[Music]
my stars
i cannot thank you all enough for coming
here to help me today
i was so worried when that order came
and asking for 12 dozen halloween cakes
a couple at a time isn't a problem and
even it doesn't it's manageable
but this is too much for me all by
myself
hey don't bet it Flora I wanted to go to
the strip club and get [ __ ]
but the others weren't feeling it so we
were all looking for something to do
today anyway
we don't mind helping you out at the
shop
yo did this let's say what I think she
said I thought we just came by for some
cupcakes
i don't care what we do as long as I'm
with Bartleby
sorry Flora but I can't help you today
although my brothers can
why not you cause my mom just bought me
this coat from jc penney's
for like 200 bucks if she found out i
got flour on it
she'd totally ground my ass
mom buys you clothes from jc penney's
mom buys all of my clothes from goodwill
mom buys your clothes bro she doesn't
buy me clothes
what about the ones you have on now
these are your hand-me-downs from when
you were seven
you were just fat do you see
he he bro put that away it's
embarrassing
give that to me I want it hey let go of
it
unhand the picture this instant Sonic
help me
oh no please stop it no fighting in the
shop
you're going to break something
ah
listen up you may look like a green
version of my bitch but that doesn't
allow you the right to speak your mind
amongst my authority
you smell like potato salad get out of
my presents or else I will end you
bro go home [ __ ] that's what I just
said [ __ ]
go home fine you know what I'm leaving
have fun with your boyfriend bro because
you're not seeing me for the rest of the
day
the Flora dad just texted and he's
throwing up
because he accidentally ate lettuce i
gotta go taken to the hospital or he
will hit me
pack your things everybody we're out of
here
we are but Mindy flory needs your help
i don't want to she's boring and ugly
if you want to stay and help this loser
you are more than welcome
but I'm not wasting my Saturday in some
disgusting bakery
when I could be out getting some ass
then why the [ __ ] did we come here then
dumb [ __ ]
Mindy you can't just leave her can you
she's your sister
if if there's something you have to do
it's probably more important that
whatever it is I have going on here
you should go and do the thing I'm sorry
for wasting your time
i'll stay late tonight after work and
try to get all of the cakes done myself
Flora you can't it's just too much
don't don't worry about it sis it'll be
fine
I'm a baker after all it's what I do you
go have fun with your friends
[Music]
okay Flora we'll help you
what what did you say we'll help you
on one condition we expect to be paid
the same amount as normal employees
paid yeah yeah of course I can totally
do that
does that mean you'll stay
[Music]
wow Knuckles I'm impressed I had no idea
you could bake so well
my great-grandfather Athair always gets
home late after going to the bar
and gay club just remember the basics
and you'll find it's pretty simple
bro I'm through decorating a whole batch
of cookies
would you mind taking them over to the
rack for me while I start on the rest
[Music]
oh dear bro it looks like you got some
pumpkin spice frosting
on your ass don't worry your handsome
bro will take care of that for you
point that ass here
[Music]
oh brother you must be a parking ticket
because you
got fine written all over you
[Music]
excuse me everyone I'm sorry to
interrupt I see you're hard at work
but I desperately need a couple of
volunteers to put on these mascot
costumes
and promote the shop out front me and my
bro can go do that
he's really good at shaking his ass what
do you say bro
let's do it no way my [ __ ] I won't
allow you to take on more work than you
already have for the day
you have worked so hard you deserve a
rest I will put on that costume
and go in your place now be a good
little bitch and go over there in the
corner and slip on this 600 trillion
dollar cookie and is made out of pure
gold
that I bought
if art levy is going out there then
there's no way I'm going the expensive
man cologne he wears is disgusting
and he'll just talk about how poor I am
Manic don't you dare talk that way about
my boyfriend
especially in front of me i'll give you
a bloody nose
what the hell do you think you're doing
hold the sign still so they can read it
I'm I'm dancing well you look [ __ ]
stop it
just stand there and do your [ __ ] job
we're not out here to have fun
you're just embarrassing yourself
wow are you serious right now you don't
even know how to hold a sign correctly
and there you go dropping it on the
floor nice going now it's all dirty
pick it up Manic why are you bullying me
I’ve only ever been nice to you my
entire life but you're just being mean
you nice to me I I'm not being mean to
you you're the only one who's ever mean
to me Manic
what's wrong what's troubling you you
want to talk about it
shut up I don't have to say anything to
you you
you're just you always act like you're
better than everybody
just because you're rich and sexy
you think that everything in this world
belongs to you
that you can just take things that
people care about away from them
but surely even you must have a heart
you know what I'm talking about right
i see so that's what it is you're mad
because I stole this picture or some
[ __ ]
that picture means the world to me it
was taken many years ago
when me and my bro were babies it was
the morning after halloween
and my bro and I were eating our
halloween candy
on halloween our mom drove us down to
the rich neighborhoods
where they were giving out not just
candy but bags off chips too
it was awesome
[Music]
hey Manic I'm all out of chips you still
have some
give them to me gunky poops
[Music]
these are gross I hate cheetos here bro
you can have one back
but I'm going to keep the rest of the
bag still because I'm still hungry
oh yeah and bro can you wipe the cheese
powder from my chin
i can't reach it haha
[Music]
thanks bro you know you're the best
i will have you no green bean I don't
give a [ __ ] about your feelings
and I didn't ask to hear your life story
this picture belongs to me now
and there is nothing you can do about it
[Music]
consider yourself lucky to be alive i
was holding back
with that punch only because you are the
brother of my bitch
had I wanted you'd be dead all right and
because you are the brother of my
bitch let me honor you with a little
word of advice you cannot make somebody
be a part of your life
if they don't want to be a part of yours
my [ __ ] may have cared for you once
but no he only cares for me and there is
nothing wrong with that
because that is how he chose to live and
he's happy with it if he's happy
and you really care about him then
shouldn't you be as well people change
and people grow you may not like it but
they may even grow
and meet other people and leave you
behind if that makes you sad
then you only have yourself to play I'm
going to go back inside
i can't leave my [ __ ] by the cookies
for too
we all know he's going to try and eat
them eventually because he's fat
wait Bartleby please give me the
picture i'll do anything
it means everything to me did I but let
me Montclair I’ve raised in give you
permission to talk to me
i will make sure you regret that no no
no no quit your whining
you sound like a poopy baby [ __ ] i
missed all of your vital organs on
purpose
so it's not like you are going to die or
anything see you
wouldn't wanna be
this is fun isn't it Mindy you and me
working together at the bakery
i wish this moment could last forever
speak for yourself I'm not having any
fun at all
the only sparks of excitement I’ve been
getting was by seeing which kitchen
utensils
i could fit in my huge ass and between
my boobs
putting that where Mindy you can't be
doing that
course I can here watch the sexy [ __ ]
hey let go no Mindy I'm serious
if the health inspector found out i
would be closed down for sure
i said let go
Mindy get up hurry your hair is on the
[Music]
stovetop
everybody move I’ve got this under
control
[Music]
hiya
are you miss Flora this your bakery
that's me I knew it I ordered a cake for
my birthday last week
and it was from your bakery it was a
strawberry ice cream cake
do you remember when it arrived it was
completely melted
it ruined no you ruined my 26th birthday
party
i was so embarrassed
here's the bill take it I'm making you
pay for the damages
not because I'm supposed to but because
i want to
that bill what for I'm the one who call
you
this is supposed to be your job you
can't do this it's not fair
i think you need to stop I'm a
firefighter [ __ ] if I want
i can set your house on fire okay
what am I going to do two thousand
dollars
i don't have the money and my bakery is
in shambles
what do I do and all the halloween
cookies that I was supposed to make
they're all gone now i'll have to start
from scratch
it's all right Flora we can start again
all that matters is nobody was hurt
do you want to go to starbucks that
always cheers me
and Mindy up when we're feeling down no
thanks my dad says you are only supposed
to go there if you are a [ __ ] or a
[ __ ]
there you are [ __ ] I’ve been looking
for you Flora
i got to have a word with you oh Mindy
you're back
you disappeared when the fire started i
feared the worst
where in the world did you go that
doesn't matter here now does it
the point is that you ruined my hair in
that Goddamn kitchen
and I want retribution and vengeance in
the form of money
or blood oh just calm down you [ __ ]
now Mindy you're hurting me
listen up [ __ ] there's only one
person
to blame for our Saturday being ruined
and it's
this this poopy head hey I think the
slack makes a valid pointer once
what do you all say we blow this
popsicle stand
if we aren't getting paid there isn't
any reason for me to stick around
even more so my bitch excellent choice
of words my lover
come on let's let's go to all-star
adventures and ride the go cuts
come my green bro let us take our leave
our business here is done i'll be right
behind you bro
you guys go on ahead I'm going to take a
[ __ ] piss in the bushes
damn can I watch haha I'm just kidding
bro see you later
i don't get it I thought having Mindy
help out at the bakery would bring us
closer together
but instead all it's seeming to do is
push us further apart
it's like she doesn't want to be near me
at all
Manic have you ever wanted to be a part
of someone else's life
even if they don't exactly want to be a
part of yours
believe me I understand I know the
feeling more than you could ever know
[Music]
but a wise man once said to me I will
have you no green bean
i don't give a [ __ ] about your feelings
let me honor you with a little word of
advice
you cannot make somebody be a part of
your life if they don't want to be a
part of your
people change and people grow you may
not like it but they may even grow
and meet other people and leave you
behind if that makes you sad
then you only have yourself to blame I'm
going to go back inside
i can't leave my [ __ ] by the cookies
for too long
we all have our own lives to live all we
can do
is live the best we can
even if that means giving up those you
may hold dear
[Music]
so
go Knuckles go don't give up you can
still catch him
as if he's totally smelling my ass hey
Knuckles sorry if it [ __ ] reeks
like [ __ ] back there can't help it I had
to pull up bush's baked beans this
morning
so I'm farting up a storm in this [ __ ]
what's up sausage head I thought you
love the smell of my big sweaty butt
they don't call me the blue blur for
nothing you are not gonna pass me that
easy [ __ ] ass
come on do it pass me I'm
I'm waiting
[Music]
get the [ __ ] out of that go-kart fatty
KKnux buddy just chill we're only
having some fun
fun what fun could I possibly be having
here behind your ass crack
i spent 12 minutes catching the draft
from your smelly butt cheeks
i want an apology tell me you're sorry
oh my God [ __ ] it
I'm taking your go-kart it's obvious you
picked the best one
you can't have mine [ __ ]
[Music]
[Applause]
for the first time
[Music]
feel your energy when our
eyes touch so familiar deep inside
like you were already my
surreal to me how you
make me feel wild and calm at the same
[Applause]
time
you